Mrs. Rabbit had four little bunnies.
Their names were Mopsy, Flopsy, Cotton-tail, and Peter.
They lived in a hole under a tree.
One day Mrs. Rabbit said, "We need bread.
I'll go into town to buy some."
She grabbed her basket and an umbrella.
Mrs. Rabbit looked at her bunnies.
"I will be back soon," she said.
"Can we go outside?" asked Peter.
"Yes," said his mother.
"But don't go into the farmer's garden.
Your father went there.
And he never came home."
"Okay, Mother," said the bunnies.
Mrs. Rabbit headed off to town.
The bunnies put on their jackets and shoes.
Then they went outside.
The four bunnies hopped down the path.
"Look over there!" said Mopsy.
"I see a blackberry bush!"
"Yum!" said Flopsy and Cotton-tail.
Flopsy, Mopsy, and Cotton-tail ran to the bush.
Peter's sisters started to pick blackberries.
"I don't want blackberries," Peter thought.
"I'm going to the farmer's garden!"